(Raj:)Hey, you totally got that right!
"E=mc2."
(Penny:)I listen.
(Penny:)I have no idea what it means,
but I listen.
(Penny:)To friendship.
To friendship.
(Sheldon(off):)Would you booze hounds
please stop that infernal clinking?!
(Sheldon(off):)And the answer
was elephant!
(Sheldon:)Mmm.
(Priya:)Leonard, sweetheart, we're
kissing, not eating hot soup.
(Bernadette:)Sorry.
(Priya(computer tone):)That's my parents
on video chat.
(Priya(computer tone):)Go hide
in the bedroom.
(Leonard:)Oh, come on!
(Leonard:)Why don't we just tell
them that we're dating?
(Priya:)Oh, we've been through this.
It's not the time.
(Leonard:)When is the time?
(Priya:)I've got five brothers
and sisters.
(Priya:)One of them is bound
to screw up real big,
(Priya:)and then I'll tell my parents
about you. Now, shoo.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Priya:)Hello, Mummy. Hello, Daddy.